# CATHLEEN GHENNE

## **HELLO**

I am a dynamic and capable front end developer with many years of experience in development, maintenance and support of applications and websites. My preferred framework is ReactJS. In my free time, I am currently learning about functional programming and Clojure.

## **SKILLS**

HTML CSS/SASS END

JavaScript
JavaScript Frameworks
(ReactJS, AngularJS, jQuery
Redux, Flow)
Bootstrap Framework
Social Media integration
(Facebook API, Twitter API)
Responsive Web Design
Mobile First Design

NodeJS BACK
MongoDB PHP
ColdFusion
SQL (Oracle, MySQL)
XML
JSON
Web Services
JAVA

WordPress CMS

Mac OS X OS Windows Linux

Git OTHER
Gulp
NPM
Webpack
Jira
Agile
Scrum

## SAY HELLO

cghenne /

in /cathleen-ghenne

cathleen.ghenne@gmail.com

00 44 (0) 7530157061

### **EXPERIENCE**

July 2016 - Present

## Lead Front-End Engineer

LifeWorks, London, UK

In addition to front-end development, I currently perform hiring, training, and mentoring for a nine person team. I am also involved in project development and oversight and have helped to improve the current operating platform.

July 2015 - July 2016

# Front-End Engineer

LifeWorks, London, UK

LifeWorks: A Global Employee Engagement Platform serving 50,000 companies with over 15 million users.

Tech stack: HTML, CSS, SASS, JavaScript, AngularJS, ReactJS, Redux, Flow, NodeJS, Webpack, Gulp, NPM, Jenkins, Clojure, ClojureScript

May 2012 - July 2015

## Senior Web Developer

Vanilla Active, London UK

Vanilla Active is a digital agency offering services to agencies and brands. We designed and implemented promotional web sites directly with brands and worked closely with advertising and marketing agencies.

Tech stack: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, AngularJS, ColdFusion, PHP, Wordpress

# CATHLEEN GHENNE

### **EXPERIENCE**

#### November 2011 - March 2012

## **Excel Expert**

Wild Media Ltd, London, UK

Wild Media Ltd is a startup in the new media area. As an Excel expert and database manager, I was in charge of optimising and automating the logistics department.

## July 2011 - November 2011

#### Consultant

De Valck Consultants by Altran Brussels, Belgium

De Valck Consultants is part of Altran group, the European leader in innovation consulting. It is the dedicated brand to Quality Assurance for the Life Science industry. I worked as an IS Validation Engineer at Baxter Healthcare.

#### **December 2008 - June 2011**

## Web Developer

BrEAST Data Center, Jules Bordet Institute Brussels, Belgium

The BrEAST data centre is a specialised clinical trials unit created in order to conduct large, international Phase III studies in breast cancer aiming to register new drugs. I worked as a web and application developer, in IT support and maintenance, and in validation of computer systems developed in-house (GCP, 21 CRF part 11).

Tech stack: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, PHP, Java, Oracle SQL, MySQL

## **EDUCATION**

## 2014 The Mobile Academy

London, UK

10 week course on the mobile industry organised by UCL (University College London) and Mobile Monday London.

## 2008 Paul Lambin Institute

Brussels, Belgium

Degree: BSc Computer Science (web services, infographic and artificial intelli-

gence)

## 2005 High School "Lycée de Berlaymont"

Waterloo, Belgium

Sciences and mathematics

## **LANGUAGES**

French: Native English: Fluent Dutch: Basic

## PERSONAL INTERESTS

Sports: Outdoor sports, squash,

badminton **Music:** Piano, guitar

Other: Travelling

#### REFERENCES

References available upon request.